Pydoc is a documentation module that
generates documentation for modules,
classes, and functions. We cover functions later
in this domain, so let’s focus on how Pydoc can
generate documentation for built-in modules.
Documentation can help people understand these
modules without running countless searches on the
web for the same information. For this example,
I am in a command prompt, and I want to get some
documentation on the built-in datetime module,
as we will use that module later in the course.
At the prompt, I will type Python -m (for module)
pydoc datetime and select the Enter key on the
keyboard. The results show many of the different
functions available within the datetime module.
Note that Pydoc can document not just built-in
modules like datetime, but also any custom
Python files you've created. Simply use the
same command format but replace 'datetime'
with the name of your Python file (minus
the '.py' extension).] I will use the Ctrl+C
keyboard shortcut to end this file. Here’s a
tip you won’t see on the exam objectives. If you
want to send this information to a text file,
we can run the same command but add a greater than
symbol and the name of a file. I will add the file
name datetime.txt, select the Enter key on the
keyboard, and then navigate to this directory,
and there is the file with all the documentation
that I can read anytime without having to scroll
through a command prompt. We have reached the end
of this section on documenting code segments. The
exam objectives do not call for any code analyses,
so for the review portion of this section,
proceed to the Review 4.1 exercise in the
project workbook and use that exercise to
enhance this 415-review file. I will share
the answer with you in the following video.